<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sabrina Benitez</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Sabrina Benitez</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Power of R and Python</title>
      <link>/post/2020/12/11/blog-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2020/12/11/blog-post/</guid>
      <description>Using the skills I learned in my computational biology course at UT Austin, I will show a simple, yet effective, way to combine the power of R and Python. NYC is one of my favorite cities to visit. I admire how diverse the city is, as well as the hustle and bustle of people moving in and out every second! For this reason, I have decided to use a dataset that holds flight data from the three NYC area airports from 2013.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 1: Risk Factors for Heart Failure</title>
      <link>/project/project1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/project1/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Title: Exploration of the relationship between heart failure and potential risk factors.
This project will explore the incidence of death due to heart failure and potential associations with risk factors, such as age, diabetes, or high blood pressure. This dataset was acquired from kaggle.com. The dataset contains various clinically assessed risk factors, such as smoker status and age. This data exploration is of interest to me, personally, because many members of my family suffer from cardiovascular disease.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 2: Modeling, Testing, and Predicting</title>
      <link>/project/project2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/project2/</guid>
      <description>Introduction This project will explore the incidence of death due to heart failure and potential associations with risk factors, such as serum creatinine and serum sodium levels. This dataset was acquired from kaggle.com and contains 299 observations. The dataset contains various clinically assessed risk factors, such as smoker status and diabetic status. This data exploration is of interest to me, personally, because many members of my family suffer from cardiovascular disease.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/</guid>
      <description> Check out some of my coding projects below:
 Wrangling &amp;amp; Exploratory Data Analysis
 Modeling, Inference, Prediction
  -- </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resume</title>
      <link>/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/resume/</guid>
      <description>  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
